Guide to the Finger Lakes Runners Club records, 1981-2010.
Finger Lakes Runners Club records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Finger Lakes Runners Club records, 1981-2010.
4750
Finger Lakes Runners Club.
1.4 cubic foot.
Memorabilia, photographs, audiotape, meeting minutes
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Board meeting minutes, race results, photographs, and T-shirts from various local races, including the Finger Lakes Marathon and Ithaca 5 & 10.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Based in Ithaca, New York, the Finger Lakes Runners Club (FLRC) organizes numerous road races, trail races, and track meets throughout the year. The club also sends teams to the Upstate New York Cross Country Series and to various regional and national championship events.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Board meeting minutes, race results, photographs and T-shirts from various local races, including the Finger Lakes Marathon and Ithaca 5 & 10.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Finger Lakes Runners Club.; Finger Lakes Marathon.; Ithaca 5 & 10.
Subjects:
Running.; Running--Training.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Audiotapes.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Subject Files
  - FLRC Board Meeting (Audiotape Recording), TR-5390 (Box 1)
  - Board Meeting Minutes (Including FLRC Constitution), 1989-1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1997-2005 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Children's Running Guide, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - RRCA Club Handbook, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - A Guide to FLRC Indoor Track, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Recognition Plaque, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - FLRC Newsletter, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - USA TF Certificate, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ithaca 5 and 10 Results and History, 1974-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ithaca 5 and 10 Results and History, 1985-2005 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - An Explosion of Trail Running - "Java Joe" Daves (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - FLRC 40th Anniversary Celebration, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Triennial Finger Lakes Trail Relay History (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Hartshore Master's Mile - Women's Times, 1981-2009 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Highlights from My Life as a Runner - G. J. Gavras (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Women's Distance Festival, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Photographs (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Race T-Shirts
  - Finger Lakes Marathon T-shirt (Box 2)
  - Virgil Mountain Madness T-shirts (4) (Box 2)
  - Ithaca 5 and 10 T-shirts, 1995; 199x (Box 2)
  - Skunk Cabbage Classic T-shirt, 2009 (Box 2)
  - Skunk Cabbage Classic T-shirt, 2010 (Box 2)
  - Finger Lakes Marathon T-shirt (Box 2)
  - 19th Finger Lakes Marathon T-shirt (Box 2)
  - 20th Finger Lakes Marathon T-shirt (Box 2)
  - 21st Finger Lakes Marathon T-shirt (Box 2)
  - Women's Distance Festival T-shirt, 2010 (Box 2)
  - Hartshorne Masters Miles T-shirt, 2009 (Box 2)
  - Forest Frolics T-shirt (Box 2)